A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1 FA389
Rockefeller Archive Center
- National Commission to Study Health Facilities Financing, January 8, 1972-January 15, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 959)
- National Committee Against Mental Illness, Inc., April 1, 1958-December 15, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 960)
- National Conference of Commissioners on Uniform State Laws, June 21, 1976-October 18, 1976 (Box 56, Folder 961)
- National Coordinating Council on Drug Abuse Education and Information, January 26, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 962)
- Cross Reference Sheets - National (E-K), February 8, 1951-December 4, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 963)
- National Endowment for the Humanities, May 19, 1977-June 27, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 964)
- National Foundation, November 13, 1963-April 2, 1964 (Box 56, Folder 965)
- National Fund for Medical Education, May 21, 1953-September 22, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 966)
- National Health Council, May 5, 1964-October 3, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 967)
- National Health Education Committee, Inc., April 24, 1959-June 13, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 968)
- National Heart, Blood Vessel, Lung and Blood Act of 1972, April 24-29, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 969)
- National Information Bureau, 1958-1969 (Box 57, Folder 970)
- National Institute for Community Development, Inc., February 24-26, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 971)
- National Institute of Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, April 1, 1975-May 5, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 972)
- National Institute of Child Health and Human Development, June 29, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 973)
- National Institute of Mental Health (National Training Laboratory in Group Development), March 27, 1953-August 12, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 974)
- National Institute of Mental Health (U. S. Department of Health Education and Welfare), September 23, 1968-June 6, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 975)
- National Institutes of Health, August 19, 1963-November 24, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 976)
- Cross Reference Sheets - National (L-Z), November 19, 1946-August 28, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 977)
- National Laboratory for Higher Education (North Carolina), March 19, 1973-April 23, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 978)
- National Library of Medicine, January 29, 1968-March 31, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 979)
- National Library of Medicine, January 29, 1968-March 31, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 980)
- National Medical Fellowships, September 18, 1959-November 13, 1980 (Box 57, Folder 981)
- National Meeting on Science, Technology and Development (Department of State, Washington, D.C.), November 29, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 982)
- National Planning Association, October 25, 1951-October 24, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 983)
- National Research Council, July 7, 1944-December 12, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 984)
- National Research Council (Commission on Human Resources Biomedical and Behavioral Research, Personnel Needs and Training), August 4, 1976 (Box 57, Folder 985)
- National Science Foundation, November 5, 1951-October 17, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 986)
- National Science Foundation, November 5, 1951-October 17, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 987)
- National Study of Medical and Surgical Quality Medical Care, July 8, 1974-August 16, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 988)
- National Tuberculosis Association, October 6, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 989)
- National University of Iran (Medical School), November 27, 1963-January 8, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 990)
- National Urban League, Inc., May 14-20, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 991)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Nationw-Naz), May 20, 1955-June 1, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 992)
- Nature Conservancy (Virginia), February 9, 1971-May 5, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 993)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Nea-Net), May 11, 1950-May 15, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 994)
- Near East College Association, January 15, 1955 (Box 58, Folder 995)
- University of Nebraska, September 17, 1952-October 28, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 996)
- Needleman, Rae, February 6, 1956-June 11, 1956 (Box 58, Folder 997)
  See Commonwealth Fund, Grant Series, Commission on Chronic Illness, Box 83, Folders 760-762.
- Negev Regional University for Health Services (Israel), December 15, 1971-January 23, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 998)
- Neighborhood Health Centers, January 19-30, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 999)
- Neighborour, Keith, December 30, 1953-November 10, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 1000)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Neu-New), December 31, 1950-September 1, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 1001)
- University of Nevada (Reno), June 7, 1977 (Box 58, Folder 1002)
- University of Nevada (Reno), June 7-14, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 1003)
- University of Nevada (School of Medical Sciences, Reno), February 7, 1968-April 21, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1004)
- New England Center for Continuing Education, January 20, 1971-March 14, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 1005)
- New England Center for Continuing Education, January 20, 1971-March 14, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 1006)
- New England Center Hospital, April 6, 1953-November 28, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 1007)
- New England Hospital Assembly, March 26-28, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 1008)
- New England Journal of Medicine, June 26, 1962-September 4, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 1009)
- New Human Services Institute (New York), June 26, 1962-September 4, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 1010)
- New Human Services Institute (New York), June 26, 1962-September 4, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 1011)
- New Jersey College of Medicine and Dentistry, July 24, 1968-May 13, 1976 (Box 59, Folder 1012)
- New Jersey Medical Dental Center, January 18-21, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 1013)
- New Jersey Neuro-Psychiatric Institute, September 4, 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1014)
- New Jersey State Welfare Council, January 29, 1952-April 11, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 1015)
- New Mexico Department of Education, October 18, 1951-May 12, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 1016)
- University of New Mexico (School of Medicine), March 16, 1956-February 15, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 1017)
- University of New Mexico (School of Medicine - Regional Medical Program), April 7-17, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 1018)
- New School of Music, Inc. (Philadelphia), November 14, 1973-October 23, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 1019)
- New School of Music, Inc. (Philadelphia), November 14, 1973-October 23, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 1020)
- Cross Reference Sheets - New (Y-Z), January 29, 1951-October 26, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 1021)
- New York Academy of Medicine, February 24, 1944-August 14, 1980 (Box 60, Folder 1022)
- New York Academy of Medicine (Eastern States Health Education Conference), September 18, 1949-April 10, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 1023)
- New York City - Governance of Voluntary Teaching Hospitals (Russell A. Nelson), 1974 (Box 60, Folder 1024)
- New York City - Health Department (Medicare-Medicaid), November 14, 1968-March 27, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 1025)
- New York City Crisis (Task Force), April 28, 1976-July 8, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 1026)
- New York City Crisis (Task Force), April 28, 1976-July 8, 1976 (Box 60, Folder 1027)
- New York City Rand Institute, April 23, 1973-September 9, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 1028)
- New York City Welfare and Health Council, April 7, 1954-February 9, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 1029)
- New York Committee for the Study of Hospital Internships and Residences, November 3, 1956-November 21, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 1030)
- New York Community Trust, February 11, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 1031)
- New York Department of Public Health (Public Health Association of New York City), June 16, 1972-September 2, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 1032)
- New York Hospital (Payne Whitney Psychiatric Clinic), June 1, 1951-November 27, 1951 (Box 61, Folder 1033)
- New York Hospital/Cornell Medical Center, August 9, 1951-June 26, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 1034)
- New York Medical College, March 7, 1969-September 8, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 1035)
- New York Medical College (Matthew Jay Freund), December 5, 1967-January 15, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 1036)
- New York Medical College (Eric H. Haight), December 5, 1972-August 28, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 1037)
- New York Medical College (Flower and Fifth Avenue Hospitals), March 4, 1970-June 21, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 1038)
- New York Medical College (Metropolitan Hospital), January 9, 1968-July 23, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 1039)
- New York Public Library, November 21, 1963-August 6, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 1040)
- New York State (Department of Health - Public Health Association, Housing Committee Renewal), September 27, 1954-November 25, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 1041)
- New York State (Division of Professional Education), January 10, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 1042)
- New York University (Center for Rehabilitation Service), December 28, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 1043)
- New York University (Graduate School of Public Administration), January 29, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 1044)
- New York University (Institute for Urban Health Affairs), June 7, 1968-September 11, 1968 (Box 61, Folder 1045)
- New York University (Institute of Physical Medicine and Physical Rehabilitation), October 23, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 1046)
- New York University (Medical Center), April 13, 1944-September 13, 1978 (Box 61, Folder 1047)
- New York University (School of Occupational Health), December 11, 1951-May 6, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 1048)
- New York Urban Coalition, Inc., April 23, 1969-September 8, 1971 (Box 61, Folder 1049)
- New Zealand University, November 8, 1954-December 22, 1954 (Box 61, Folder 1050)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Newa-Ney), August 2, 1952-June 2, 1981 (Box 62, Folder 1051)
- Newberger, Eli H. (Children's Hospital Medical Center, Boston), June 15-21, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 1052)
- Newton, J. Quigg, December 11, 1952-January 3, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 1053)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ni), November 3, 1952-November 6, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 1054)
- Nicholai, Armand M., Jr., September 20, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 1055)
- Nichos, Buford L., June 30, 1972-April 30, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 1056)
- Nixon, Robert E., No Date (Box 62, Folder 1057)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Noa-Norr), May 19, 1952-July 31, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 1058)
- Nobel Prize, April 14, 1950-April 7, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 1059)
- Nomura Research Institute, June 11, 1976-July 28, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 1060)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Nort-Norw), November 22, 1950-April 24, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 1061)
- State of North Carolina, June 8, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 1062)
- University of North Carolina, February 19, 1951-September 22, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 1063)
- University of North Carolina, February 19, 1951-September 22, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 1064)
- University of North Carolina, February 19, 1951-September 22, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 1065)
- University of North Carolina, February 19, 1951-September 22, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 1066)
- University of North Carolina (Health Service Research and Development Center - Dr. Sheps), February 6, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 1067)
- University of North Carolina (Institute for Research in Social Science - Division of Health Affairs), January 23, 1951-July 1, 1957 (Box 63, Folder 1068)
- North Central New Mexico Comprehensive Health Planning Council, February 1, 1972-March 21, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 1069)
- Northeastern University, March 13, 1964-July 3, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 1070)
- Northern New England Academy Inc. (New Hampshire), December 22, 1970-January 4, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 1071)
- Northwestern University (Medical School), May 8, 1947-June 26, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 1072)
- Norwich University, April 24, 1975-November 10, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 1073)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Nos-Ny), May 2, 1949-August 31, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 1074)
- University of Notre Dame, November 4, 1970-March 25, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 1075)
- University of Nottingham (England), November 23, 1964-May 27, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 1076)
- Nova University - New York Institute of Technology (Fort Lauderdale, Florida), March 28, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 1077)
- Nuffield Provincial Hospitals Trust (London), September 11, 1969-August 30, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 1078)
- Nutritional Education, September 16, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 1079)
- Nutrition Foundation, Inc., January 16, 1973-July 8, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 1080)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Oa-Oc), March 1, 1951-October 10, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 1081)
- Oberlin College and Oberlin Health Center, April 19, 1949-April 6, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 1082)
- Occupational Medicine (Harriet L. Hardy, Occupational Service), April 18, 1969-May 20, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 1083)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Od-Ok), March 5, 1951-April 20, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 1084)
- Office of Economic Opportunity, October 18, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 1085)
- Office of Economic Opportunity (Edna Rostow), January 16, 1968-March 4, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 1086)
- Ohio State University, December 4, 1969-June 12, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 1087)
- Oklahoma Public Health Association, August 18, 1952-October 14, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 1088)
- University of Oklahoma, April 22, 1952-December 9, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 1089)
- University of Oklahoma (Medical Center - James L. Luke, State Medical Examiner), September 1, 1967-May 31, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 1090)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ol-On), February 27, 1951-October 31, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1091)
- Olmsted, Richard W. (University of Oregon, Medical School), December 4, 1967-March 28, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 1092)
- Ontario Science Center (Taizo Miake), October 25, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 1093)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Op-Ori), October 9, 1951-July 15, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1094)
- Operation Crossroads Africa, Inc. (Francis D. Rogers and James G. Rogers), November 10, 1970-March 18, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 1095)
- Operations Coordinating Board, June 21, 1954-April 25, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 1096)
- Opler, Marvin, April 28, 1958-December 3, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 1097)
- University of Oregon, December 30, 1954-April 23, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1098)
- Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (Paris), October 27, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 1099)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Orl-Os), February 27, 1951-February 15, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 1100)
- Orr, Richard H., May 3, 1973-October 2, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 1101)
- Oster, Allan W., February 11, 1953-May 15, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 1102)
- Osteopathy, January 2, 1968-September 27, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 1103)
- Ostow, Mortimer, November 14, 1956-January 7, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 1104)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Pri), February 1, 1951-December 18, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 1105)
- Primary Medical Communications, Inc., March 16-21, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 1106)
- School of Primary Physicians (Tufts, New England), November 28, 1972-August 14, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 1107)
- Prince Albert Community Clinic (Saskatchewan), December 9, 1968-January 13, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1108)
- Princeton University Press (Woodrow Wilson), June 1, 1972-July 17, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 1109)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Pro), November 26, 1946-February 20, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 1110)
- Professional Studies Institute, August 28, 1963-September 9, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 1111)
- Proger, Samuel (New England Medical Center Hospital), December 21, 1955-July 1, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 1112)
- Project Hear (Palo Alto, California), Deember 1-8, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1113)
- Project Hope (William B. Walsh), April 15, 1970-February 12, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 1114)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Pru-Ps), March 20, 1951-October 11, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 1115)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Pu-Py), May 12, 1949-November 2, 1981 (Box 65, Folder 1116)
- Public Opinion and Public Policy (Public Attitudes Towards Cities and Their Future), November 1, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 1117)
- Public Record, May 6, 1971-June 8, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1118)
- Commonwealth of Puerto Rico, May 28, 1974-June 19, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 1119)
- University of Puerto Rico, November 20, 1956-February 6, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 1120)
- University of Puerto Rico School of Medicine - Health Sciences Communication, Jerry H. Anderson), February 1, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 1121)
- Putt, S. Gorley, June 1, 1951-February 29, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 1122)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Q), October 29, 1952-July 15, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1123)
- Queens College (Charlotte, North Carolina), July 24, 1963-January 18, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 1124)
- Queens College (Oxford, England), July 24, 1963-January 18, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 1125)
- Borough of Queens Medical School (President's Committee, New York), September 13, 1972-February 25, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 1126)
- University of Queensland (St. Lucia, Australia), August 28, 1974-September 10, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 1127)
- Quick, Donald (University of Florence, Medical School), May 22, 1968-June 7, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 1128)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Raa-Rah), October 10, 1952-April 30, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1129)
- Radcliff Institute, February 28, 1967-February 6, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 1130)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rai-Ran), July 12, 1951-March 21, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 1131)
- Rand Corporation, January 11, 1969-June 21, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 1132)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rap-Ray), January 20, 1950-March 9, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 1133)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rea-Ref), January 1, 1948-August 18, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1134)
- Reader, George, January 29, 1951-December 15, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 1135)
- Reed College, February 23, 1956-December 15, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 1136)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Reg-Rein), November 13, 1950-April 2, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 1137)
- Division of Regional Medical Programs (Department of Health, Education and Welfare), June 14, 1968-July 22, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 1138)
- Regional Plan Association (New York), May 13, 1970-August 1, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 1139)
- Rehabilitation Institute of Chicago, April 25, 1974-September 8, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 1140)
- Registered Nurse (National Magazine for Nurses), July 31, 1972-August 9, 1972 (Box 67, Folder 1141)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Reis-Rep), January 26, 1950-August 20, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1142)
- Reproductive Biology and Contraceptive Development, February 13, 1972-April 3, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 1143)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Res-Rh), October 21, 1942-April 24, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1144)
- Research and Design Institute (Providence, Rhode Island), July 15, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 1145)
- Research Corporation (New York), September 21, 1970-September 16, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 1146)
- Research Council for Economic Security, September 12, 1950-December 10, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1147)
- Research Foundation of Children's Hospital (Washington, D.C.), October 30, 1970-December 3, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 1148)
- Research in Medical Care of the Aging, No Date (Box 67, Folder 1149)
- Review - Future Material to be Reviewed Periodically Per Memorandum, January 13, 1981-April 6, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1150)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Ric), June 13, 1951-November 4, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1151)
- Rice University, October 2, 1974-November 8, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 1152)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rid-Rim), February 21, 1952-December 10, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 1153)
- Ridenour, Nina, October 27, 1960-September 16, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1154)
- Riggs Center, Austin, October 10, 1958-June 24, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 1155)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rin-Riz), October 21, 1948-April 4, 1979 (Box 67, Folder 1156)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Roa-Roberts), April 2, 1951-April 3, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1157)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Roberts-Robs), April 12, 1951-February 23, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1158)
- Robinson, William D. (University of Michigan, Medical Center), August 22, 1967-October 9, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 1159)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Roc), October 1, 1947-January 15, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 1160)
- Rochester Institute of Technology, July 7, 1959-January 22, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 1161)
- University of Rochester, January 30, 1953-December 5, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1162)
- University of Rochester, January 1, 1974-February 8, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 1163)
- University of Rochester (Lagos University of Nigeria), March 16, 1962-April 3, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 1164)
- University of Rochester (School of Medicine and Dentistry - Harry L. Segal), October 22, 1968-February 6, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 1165)
- Rockefeller University, June 2, 1970-September 5, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 1166)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rod-Rog), January 24, 1950-September 14, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 1167)
- Rogers, Constance (Intermediate School #201), March 21, 1969-June 30, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 1168)
- Rogers, David E. (Robert Wood Johnson Foundation), February 1-16, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 1169)
- Rogers, Francis Day, September 22, 1970-February 15, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 1170)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Roh-Rop), October 1, 1947-October 19, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 1171)
- Rohrbaugh, Lewis H., January 8, 1973-February 28, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 1172)
- Roosevelt Hospital, December 29, 1970-December 1, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 1173)
- Roosevelt Hospital, December 29, 1970-December 1, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 1174)
- Roosevelt Hospital (Advance Disease Service - Direct Patient Services), October 3, 1974-October 5, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 1175)
- Roosevelt Hospital/St. Luke's Hospital Center, April 13, 1976-March 3, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 1176)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rose), July 12, 1951-July 22, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 1177)
- Rosen, George, May 26, 1953-April 14, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 1178)
- Rosen, Helen, December 11, 1975-January 8, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 1179)
- Rosen, John N., January 22, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 1180)
- Rosenbaum, Milton, May 16, 1952-April 5, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 1181)
- Rosenfeld, Albert, September 23, 1972-February 1, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 1182)
- Rosenstial Basic Medical Sciences Research Center (Brandeis University), November 29, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 1183)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rosi-Rosw), October 2, 1951-March 3, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1184)
- Rosinski, Edward F. (University of Connecticut), May 3, 1957-June 30, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 1185)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rot-Roz), April 21, 1947-July 29, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1186)
- Royal College of Physicians, October 18, 1954-June 25, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 1187)
- Royal College of Surgeons Foundation, Inc., March 1, 1968-August 25, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 1188)
- Royal Society of Medicine/Royal Society of Medicine Foundation, Inc., March 14, 1957-June 15, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 1189)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rub-Rus), February 26, 1940-September 2, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1190)
- Rural Area Practice (Illinois Program), July 31, 1950-February 28, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 1191)
- Rural Hospital Program, September 15, 1931-February 27, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 1192)
- Rural Hospital Program, September 15, 1931-February 27, 1962 (Box 69, Folder 1193)
- Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center, November 21, 1968-June 14, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 1194)
- Rusk, Howard A., Jr., August 13, 1965-September 24, 1976 (Box 69, Folder 1195)
- Russelton Medical Group, October 23-27, 1958 (Box 69, Folder 1196)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Rut-Ry), October 15, 1951-January 21, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1197)
- Rutgers University (Center for Infancy and Early Childhood - Graduate School of Education), June 5-21, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 1198)
- Rutgers University (Medical School), July 24, 1961-September 7, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 1199)
- Rutland Amateur Hockey Association, Inc. (Christopher A. Webber, Jr.), February 11, 1976-September 2, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 1200)
- Rutstein, David D., March 12, 1951-May 28, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1201)
- Rymer, Charles A., May 29, 1970-June 15, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 1202)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Saa-Sah), April 5, 1951-October 21, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1203)
- Sabah, Nassir, March 4, 1968-July 13, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 1204)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sai-Sal), May 28, 1952-April 9, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 1205)
- University of Saint Andrews, September 24, 1956-March 4, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1206)
- Saint Louis University, September 16, 1963-August 21, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 1207)
- Saint Louis University, September 16, 1963-August 21, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 1208)
- Saint Mark's Clinic (New York City), August 31, 1971-October 25, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 1209)
- Salk Institute, April 2, 1964-January 8, 1976 (Box 70, Folder 1210)
- Cross Reference Sheets (Sam-San), October 13, 1949-July 17, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 1211)
- Samaritan Health Service (Phoenix, Arizona), June 29, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 1212)